Guide to the HERE General Secretary-Treasurer's Files on Microfilm, 1907-1993
HERE General Secretary-Treasurer's Files on Microfilm.
- Series General Secretary-Treasurer. Local Correspondence. 1988-1990.
  - Local 251, 1988-1990; 48 (Reel 49)
    Beginning at frame 02204 on Correspondence reel 10.
  - Local 261, 1988-1990; 49 (Reel 49)
    Beginning at frame 02223 on Correspondence reel 10.
  - Local 264, 1988-1990; 50 (Reel 49)
    Beginning at frame 02310 on Correspondence reel 10.
  - Local 270, 1988-1990; 51 (Reel 49)
    Beginning at frame 02318 on Correspondence reel 10.
  - Local 272, 1988-1990; 52 (Reel 49)
    Beginning at frame 02329 on Correspondence reel 10.
  - Local 274, 1988-1990; 53 (Reel 49)
    Beginning at frame 02336 on Correspondence reel 10.
  - Local 280, 1988-1990; 54 (Reel 49)
    Beginning at frame 02381 on Correspondence reel 10.
  - Local 301, 1988-1990; 55 (Reel 49)
    Beginning at frame 02397 on Correspondence reel 10.
  - Local 309, 1988-1990; 1 (Reel 50)
    Beginning at frame 00005 on Correspondence reel 11.
  - Local 310, 1988-1990; 2 (Reel 50)
    Beginning at frame 00028 on Correspondence reel 11.
  - Local 312, 1988-1990; 3 (Reel 50)
    Beginning at frame 00031 on Correspondence reel 11.
  - Local 315, 1988-1990; 4 (Reel 50)
    Beginning at frame 00177 on Correspondence reel 11.
  - Local 340, 1988-1990; 5 (Reel 50)
    Beginning at frame 00179 on Correspondence reel 11.
  - Local 353, 1988-1990; 6 (Reel 50)
    Beginning at frame 00192 on Correspondence reel 11.
  - Local 355, 1988-1990; 7 (Reel 50)
    Beginning at frame 00229 on Correspondence reel 11.
  - Local 360, 1988-1990; 8 (Reel 50)
    Beginning at frame 00292 on Correspondence reel 11.
  - Local 361, 1988-1990; 9 (Reel 50)
    Beginning at frame 00301 on Correspondence reel 11.
  - Local 369, 1988-1990; 10 (Reel 50)
    Beginning at frame 00309 on Correspondence reel 11.
  - Local 391, 1988-1990; 11 (Reel 50)
    Beginning at frame 00320 on Correspondence reel 11.
  - Local 400, 1988-1990; 12 (Reel 50)
    Beginning at frame 00333 on Correspondence reel 11.
  - Local 414, 1988-1990; 13 (Reel 50)
    Beginning at frame 00336 on Correspondence reel 11.
  - Local 427, 1988-1990; 14 (Reel 50)
    Beginning at frame 00376 on Correspondence reel 11.
  - Local 436, 1988-1990; 15 (Reel 50)
    Beginning at frame 00398 on Correspondence reel 11.
  - Local 441, 1988-1990; 16 (Reel 50)
    Beginning at frame 00403 on Correspondence reel 11.
  - Local 442, 1988-1990; 17 (Reel 50)
    Beginning at frame 00442 on Correspondence reel 11.
  - Local 450, 1988-1990; 18 (Reel 50)
    Beginning at frame 00487 on Correspondence reel 11.
  - Local 457, 1988-1990; 19 (Reel 50)
    Beginning at frame 00505 on Correspondence reel 11.
  - Local 466, 1988-1990; 20 (Reel 50)
    Beginning at frame 00518 on Correspondence reel 11.
  - Local 471, 1988-1990; 21 (Reel 50)
    Beginning at frame 00569 on Correspondence reel 11.
  - Local 479, 1988-1990; 22 (Reel 50)
    Beginning at frame 00571 on Correspondence reel 11.
  - Local 483, 1988-1990; 23 (Reel 50)
    Beginning at frame 00597 on Correspondence reel 11.
  - Local 497, 1988-1990; 24 (Reel 50)
    Beginning at frame 00604 on Correspondence reel 11.
  - Local 498, 1988-1990; 25 (Reel 50)
    Beginning at frame 00616 on Correspondence reel 11.
  - Local 509, 1988-1990; 26 (Reel 50)
    Beginning at frame 00638 on Correspondence reel 11.
  - Local 531, 1988-1990; 27 (Reel 50)
    Beginning at frame 00674 on Correspondence reel 11.
  - Local 533, 1988-1990; 28 (Reel 50)
    Beginning at frame 00739 on Correspondence reel 11.
  - Local 535, 1988-1990; 29 (Reel 50)
    Beginning at frame 00798 on Correspondence reel 11.
  - Local 541, 1988-1990; 30 (Reel 50)
    Beginning at frame 00804 on Correspondence reel 11.
  - Local 550, 1988-1990; 31 (Reel 50)
    Beginning at frame 00843 on Correspondence reel 11.
  - Local 590, 1988-1990; 32 (Reel 50)
    Beginning at frame 00850 on Correspondence reel 11.
  - Local 604, 1988-1990; 33 (Reel 50)
    Beginning at frame 00871 on Correspondence reel 11.
  - Local 610, 1988-1990; 34 (Reel 50)
    Beginning at frame 00896 on Correspondence reel 11.
  - Local 611, 1988-1990; 35 (Reel 50)
    Beginning at frame 00933 on Correspondence reel 11.
  - Local 623, 1988-1990; 36 (Reel 50)
    Beginning at frame 00937 on Correspondence reel 11.
  - Local 628, 1988-1990; 37 (Reel 50)
    Beginning at frame 00952 on Correspondence reel 11.
  - Local 631, 1988-1990; 38 (Reel 50)
    Beginning at frame 00965 on Correspondence reel 11.
  - Local 634, 1988-1990; 39 (Reel 50)
    Beginning at frame 00987 on Correspondence reel 11.
  - Local 636, 1988-1990; 40 (Reel 50)
    Beginning at frame 01015 on Correspondence reel 11.
  - Local 662, 1988-1990; 41 (Reel 50)
    Beginning at frame 01034 on Correspondence reel 11.
  - Local 681, 1988-1990; 42 (Reel 50)
    Beginning at frame 01109 on Correspondence reel 11.
  - Local 703, 1988-1990; 43 (Reel 50)
    Beginning at frame 01119 on Correspondence reel 11.
  - Local 719, 1988-1990; 44 (Reel 50)
    Beginning at frame 01125 on Correspondence reel 11.
  - Local 727, 1988-1990; 45 (Reel 50)
    Beginning at frame 01147 on Correspondence reel 11.
  - Local 737, 1988-1990; 46 (Reel 50)
    Beginning at frame 01177 on Correspondence reel 11.
  - Local 767, 1988-1990; 47 (Reel 50)
    Beginning at frame 01223 on Correspondence reel 11.
  - Local 772, 1988-1990; 48 (Reel 50)
    Beginning at frame 01242 on Correspondence reel 11.
  - Local 775, 1988-1990; 49 (Reel 50)
    Beginning at frame 01273 on Correspondence reel 11.
  - Local 779, 1988-1990; 50 (Reel 50)
    Beginning at frame 01299 on Correspondence reel 11.
  - Local 791, 1988-1990; 51 (Reel 50)
    Beginning at frame 01303 on Correspondence reel 11.
  - Local 803, 1988-1990; 52 (Reel 50)
    Beginning at frame 01319 on Correspondence reel 11.
  - Local 804, 1988-1990; 53 (Reel 50)
    Beginning at frame 01325 on Correspondence reel 11.
  - Local 806, 1988-1990; 54 (Reel 50)
    Beginning at frame 01328 on Correspondence reel 11.
  - Local 814, 1988-1990; 55 (Reel 50)
    Beginning at frame 01377 on Correspondence reel 11.
  - Local 847, 1988-1990; 56 (Reel 50)
    Beginning at frame 01414 on Correspondence reel 11.
  - Local 863, 1988-1990; 57 (Reel 50)
    Beginning at frame 01430 on Correspondence reel 11.
  - Local 878, 1988-1990; 58 (Reel 50)
    Beginning at frame 01471 on Correspondence reel 11.
  - Local 879, 1988-1990; 59 (Reel 50)
    Beginning at frame 01518 on Correspondence reel 11.
  - Local 886, 1988-1990; 60 (Reel 50)
    Beginning at frame 01524 on Correspondence reel 11.
  - I.P.S.S.E.U., 1988-1990; 61 (Reel 50)
    Beginning at frame 01682 on Correspondence reel 11.
  - California. S.C., 1985-1990; 62 (Reel 50)
    Beginning at frame 01782 on Correspondence reel 11.
  - Illinois. S.C., 1979-1986; 63 (Reel 50)
    Beginning at frame 01805 on Correspondence reel 11.
  - Minnesota. S.C., 1988-1990; 64 (Reel 50)
    Beginning at frame 01813 on Correspondence reel 11.
  - Montana. S.C., 1984-1990; 65 (Reel 50)
    Beginning at frame 01834 on Correspondence reel 11.
  - New Jersey. S.C., 1984-1989; 66 (Reel 50)
    Beginning at frame 01840 on Correspondence reel 11.
  - New York. S.C., 1982-1986; 67 (Reel 50)
    Beginning at frame 01844 on Correspondence reel 11.
  - Ohio. S.C., 1982-1988; 68 (Reel 50)
    Beginning at frame 01863 on Correspondence reel 11.
  - Pennsylvania. S.C., 1982; 69 (Reel 50)
    Beginning at frame 01866 on Correspondence reel 11.
  - Washington., 1982-1985; 70 (Reel 50)
    Beginning at frame 01877 on Correspondence reel 11.
  - Wisconsin., 1982-1989; 71 (Reel 50)
    Beginning at frame 01899 on Correspondence reel 11.
- Series General Secretary-Treasurer. Local Correspondence. 1991.
  - Local 1., 1991; 1 (Reel 51)
    Beginning at frame 00005 on Correspondence reel 12.
  - Local 2, 1991; 2 (Reel 51)
    Beginning at frame 00014 on Correspondence reel 12.
  - Local 3., 1991; 3 (Reel 51)
    Beginning at frame 00062 on Correspondence reel 12.
  - Local 4, 1991; 4 (Reel 51)
    Beginning at frame 00119 on Correspondence reel 12.
  - Local 5, 1991; 5 (Reel 51)
    Beginning at frame 00127 on Correspondence reel 12.
  - Local 5. Kaloko II Partnership., 1991; 6 (Reel 51)
    Beginning at frame 00215 on Correspondence reel 12.
  - Local 6, 1991; 7 (Reel 51)
    Beginning at frame 00292 on Correspondence reel 12.
  - Local 7, 1991; 8 (Reel 51)
    Beginning at frame 00847 on Correspondence reel 12.
  - Local 8, 1991; 9 (Reel 51)
    Beginning at frame 00857 on Correspondence reel 12.
  - Local 9, 1991; 10 (Reel 51)
    Beginning at frame 00869 on Correspondence reel 12.
  - Local 10, 1991; 11 (Reel 51)
    Beginning at frame 00884 on Correspondence reel 12.
  - Local 11, 1991; 12 (Reel 51)
    Beginning at frame 00891 on Correspondence reel 12.
  - Local 11. DOL Inquiry., 1991; 13 (Reel 51)
    Beginning at frame 00928 on Correspondence reel 12.
  - Local 11. Registry Hotel., 1991; 14 (Reel 51)
    Beginning at frame 01005 on Correspondence reel 12.
  - Local 11. Carnegie Deli., 1991; 15 (Reel 51)
    Beginning at frame 01085 on Correspondence reel 12.
  - Local 12, 1991; 16 (Reel 51)
    Beginning at frame 01131 on Correspondence reel 12.
  - Local 14, 1991; 17 (Reel 51)
    Beginning at frame 01138 on Correspondence reel 12.
  - Local 15, 1991; 18 (Reel 51)
    Beginning at frame 01143 on Correspondence reel 12.
  - Local 15. So. Ill. Vs. Pere Margqette., 1991; 19 (Reel 51)
    Beginning at frame 01157 on Correspondence reel 12.
  - Local 16, 1991; 20 (Reel 51)
    Beginning at frame 01265 on Correspondence reel 12.
  - Local 17, 1991; 21 (Reel 51)
    Beginning at frame 01287 on Correspondence reel 12.
  - Local 18, 1991; 22 (Reel 51)
    Beginning at frame 01310 on Correspondence reel 12.
  - Local 19, 1991; 23 (Reel 51)
    Beginning at frame 01314 on Correspondence reel 12.
  - Local 19. Trusteeship., 1991; 24 (Reel 51)
    Beginning at frame 01349 on Correspondence reel 12.
  - Local 19. Trusteeship., 1989; 25 (Reel 51)
    Beginning at frame 01457 on Correspondence reel 12.
  - Local 19. Trusteeship., 1989-1991; 26 (Reel 51)
    Beginning at frame 01694 on Correspondence reel 12.
  - Local 19. Fragnito Appeal., 1991; 1 (Reel 52)
    Beginning at frame 00005 on Correspondence reel 13.
  - Local 20, 1991; 2 (Reel 52)
    Beginning at frame 00449 on Correspondence reel 13.
  - Local 21, 1991; 3 (Reel 52)
    Beginning at frame 00461 on Correspondence reel 13.
  - Local 24, 1991; 4 (Reel 52)
    Beginning at frame 00476 on Correspondence reel 13.
  - Local 25, 1991; 5 (Reel 52)
    Beginning at frame 00409 on Correspondence reel 13.
  - Local 26, 1991; 6 (Reel 52)
    Beginning at frame 00417 on Correspondence reel 13.
  - Local 28, 1991; 7 (Reel 52)
    Beginning at frame 00547 on Correspondence reel 13.
  - Local 29, 1991; 8 (Reel 52)
    Beginning at frame 00557 on Correspondence reel 13.
  - Local 30, 1991; 9 (Reel 52)
    Beginning at frame 00561 on Correspondence reel 13.
  - Local 31, 1991; 10 (Reel 52)
    Beginning at frame 00573 on Correspondence reel 13.
  - Local 32, 1991; 11 (Reel 52)
    Beginning at frame 00594 on Correspondence reel 13.
  - Local 34. Strike Payments., 1984; 12 (Reel 52)
    Beginning at frame 00609 on Correspondence reel 13.
  - Local 34. Yale Strike Pay., 1984; 13 (Reel 52)
    Beginning at frame 00909 on Correspondence reel 13.
  - Local 34. Yale Strike Pay., 1984; 14 (Reel 52)
    Beginning at frame 01210 on Correspondence reel 13.
  - Local 34. Yale Strike Pay., 1984; 15 (Reel 52)
    Beginning at frame 01543 on Correspondence reel 13.
  - Local 34. Yale Strike Pay., 1984; 16 (Reel 52)
    Beginning at frame 01849 on Correspondence reel 13.
  - Local 34. Yale Strike Pay., 1984; 17 (Reel 52)
    Beginning at frame 02177 on Correspondence reel 13.
  - Local 34. Yale Strike Pay., 1984; 18 (Reel 52)
    Beginning at frame 02490 on Correspondence reel 13.
  - Local 34. Yale Strike Pay., 1984; 1 (Reel 53)
    Beginning at frame 00005 on Correspondence reel 14.
  - Local 34. New Haven, CT., 1984; 2 (Reel 53)
    Beginning at frame 00312 on Correspondence reel 14.
  - Local 34. Yale Strike Pay., 1984; 3 (Reel 53)
    Beginning at frame 00340 on Correspondence reel 14.
  - Local 35, 1991; 4 (Reel 53)
    Beginning at frame 00651 on Correspondence reel 14.
  - Local 36, 1991; 5 (Reel 53)
    Beginning at frame 00656 on Correspondence reel 14.
  - Local 40, 1991; 6 (Reel 53)
    Beginning at frame 00660 on Correspondence reel 14.
  - Local 436, 1991; 7 (Reel 53)
    Beginning at frame 00718 on Correspondence reel 14.
  - Local 47, 1991; 8 (Reel 53)
    Beginning at frame 00758 on Correspondence reel 14.
  - Local 49, 1991; 9 (Reel 53)
    Beginning at frame 00762 on Correspondence reel 14.
  - Local 50, 1991; 10 (Reel 53)
    Beginning at frame 00829 on Correspondence reel 14.
  - Local 51, 1991; 11 (Reel 53)
    Beginning at frame 00864 on Correspondence reel 14.
  - Local 54, 1991; 12 (Reel 53)
    Beginning at frame 00871 on Correspondence reel 14.
  - Local 56, 1991; 13 (Reel 53)
    Beginning at frame 00932 on Correspondence reel 14.
  - Local 57, 1991; 14 (Reel 53)
    Beginning at frame 00945 on Correspondence reel 14.
  - Local 62, 1991; 15 (Reel 53)
    Beginning at frame 00952 on Correspondence reel 14.
  - Local 64, 1991; 16 (Reel 53)
    Beginning at frame 00956 on Correspondence reel 14.
  - Local 65, 1991; 17 (Reel 53)
    Beginning at frame 00963 on Correspondence reel 14.
  - Local 69, 1991; 18 (Reel 53)
    Beginning at frame 00983 on Correspondence reel 14.
  - Local 70, 1991; 19 (Reel 53)
    Beginning at frame 01002 on Correspondence reel 14.
  - Local 72, 1991; 20 (Reel 53)
    Beginning at frame 01041 on Correspondence reel 14.
  - Local 73, 1991; 21 (Reel 53)
    Beginning at frame 01049 on Correspondence reel 14.
  - Local 74, 1991; 22 (Reel 53)
    Beginning at frame 01087 on Correspondence reel 14.
  - Local 75, 1991; 23 (Reel 53)
    Beginning at frame 01096 on Correspondence reel 14.
  - Local 76, 1991; 24 (Reel 53)
    Beginning at frame 01154 on Correspondence reel 14.
  - Local 77, 1991; 25 (Reel 53)
    Beginning at frame 01157 on Correspondence reel 14.
  - Local 84, 1991; 26 (Reel 53)
    Beginning at frame 01165 on Correspondence reel 14.
  - Local 86, 1991; 27 (Reel 53)
    Beginning at frame 01198 on Correspondence reel 14.
  - Local 99, 1991; 28 (Reel 53)
    Beginning at frame 01207 on Correspondence reel 14.
  - Local 100, 1991; 29 (Reel 53)
    Beginning at frame 01218 on Correspondence reel 14.
  - Local 101, 1991; 30 (Reel 53)
    Beginning at frame 01270 on Correspondence reel 14.
  - Local 104, 1991; 31 (Reel 53)
    Beginning at frame 01278 on Correspondence reel 14.
  - Local 118, 1991; 32 (Reel 53)
    Beginning at frame 01285 on Correspondence reel 14.
  - Local 122, 1991; 33 (Reel 53)
    Beginning at frame 01294 on Correspondence reel 14.
  - Local 126, 1991; 34 (Reel 53)
    Beginning at frame 01309 on Correspondence reel 14.
  - Local 135, 1991; 35 (Reel 53)
    Beginning at frame 01317 on Correspondence reel 14.
  - Local 146, 1991; 36 (Reel 53)
    Beginning at frame 01324 on Correspondence reel 14.
  - Local 151, 1991; 37 (Reel 53)
    Beginning at frame 01328 on Correspondence reel 14.
  - Local 155, 1991; 38 (Reel 53)
    Beginning at frame 01338 on Correspondence reel 14.
  - Local 165, 1991; 39 (Reel 53)
    Beginning at frame 01359 on Correspondence reel 14.
  - Local 166, 1991; 40 (Reel 53)
    Beginning at frame 01370 on Correspondence reel 14.
  - Local 181, 1991; 41 (Reel 53)
    Beginning at frame 01393 on Correspondence reel 14.
  - Local 200, 1991; 42 (Reel 53)
    Beginning at frame 01417 on Correspondence reel 14.
  - Local 206, 1991; 43 (Reel 53)
    Beginning at frame 01420 on Correspondence reel 14.
  - Local 215, 1991; 44 (Reel 53)
    Beginning at frame 01429 on Correspondence reel 14.
  - Local 217, 1991; 45 (Reel 53)
    Beginning at frame 01433 on Correspondence reel 14.
  - Local 225, 1991; 46 (Reel 53)
    Beginning at frame 01454 on Correspondence reel 14.
  - Local 226., 1991; 47 (Reel 53)
    Beginning at frame 01457 on Correspondence reel 14.
  - Local 246, 1991; 48 (Reel 53)
    Beginning at frame 01532 on Correspondence reel 14.
  - Local 251, 1991; 49 (Reel 53)
    Beginning at frame 01542 on Correspondence reel 14.
  - Local 261, 1991; 50 (Reel 53)
    Beginning at frame 01558 on Correspondence reel 14.
  - Local 264, 1991; 51 (Reel 53)
    Beginning at frame 01577 on Correspondence reel 14.
  - Local 270, 1991; 52 (Reel 53)
    Beginning at frame 01586 on Correspondence reel 14.
  - Local 272, 1991; 53 (Reel 53)
    Beginning at frame 01601 on Correspondence reel 14.
  - Local 274, 1991; 54 (Reel 53)
    Beginning at frame 01604 on Correspondence reel 14.
  - Local 280, 1991; 55 (Reel 53)
    Beginning at frame 01613 on Correspondence reel 14.
  - Local 281, 1991; 56 (Reel 53)
    Beginning at frame 01620 on Correspondence reel 14.
  - Local 301, 1991; 57 (Reel 53)
    Beginning at frame 01623 on Correspondence reel 14.
  - Local 309, 1991; 58 (Reel 53)
    Beginning at frame 01631 on Correspondence reel 14.
  - Local 310, 1991; 59 (Reel 53)
    Beginning at frame 01639 on Correspondence reel 14.
  - Local 315, 1991; 60 (Reel 53)
    Beginning at frame 01642 on Correspondence reel 14.
  - Local 332, 1991; 61 (Reel 53)
    Beginning at frame 01645 on Correspondence reel 14.
  - Local 340, 1991; 62 (Reel 53)
    Beginning at frame 01648 on Correspondence reel 14.
  - Local 353, 1991; 63 (Reel 53)
    Beginning at frame 01662 on Correspondence reel 14.
  - Local 355, 1991; 64 (Reel 53)
    Beginning at frame 01671 on Correspondence reel 14.
  - Local 360, 1991; 65 (Reel 53)
    Beginning at frame 01707 on Correspondence reel 14.
  - Local 361, 1991; 66 (Reel 53)
    Beginning at frame 01721 on Correspondence reel 14.
  - Local 369, 1991; 67 (Reel 53)
    Beginning at frame 01726 on Correspondence reel 14.
  - Local 391, 1991; 68 (Reel 53)
    Beginning at frame 01734 on Correspondence reel 14.
  - Local 400, 1991; 69 (Reel 53)
    Beginning at frame 01739 on Correspondence reel 14.
  - Local 401, 1991; 70 (Reel 53)
    Beginning at frame 01750 on Correspondence reel 14.
  - Local 414, 1991; 71 (Reel 53)
    Beginning at frame 01760 on Correspondence reel 14.
  - Local 427, 1991; 72 (Reel 53)
    Beginning at frame 01772 on Correspondence reel 14.
  - Local 436, 1991; 73 (Reel 53)
    Beginning at frame 01779 on Correspondence reel 14.
  - Local 441, 1991; 74 (Reel 53)
    Beginning at frame 01789 on Correspondence reel 14.
  - Local 442, 1991; 75 (Reel 53)
    Beginning at frame 01792 on Correspondence reel 14.
  - Local 450, 1991; 76 (Reel 53)
    Beginning at frame 01806 on Correspondence reel 14.
  - Local 457, 1991; 77 (Reel 53)
    Beginning at frame 01826 on Correspondence reel 14.
  - Local 466, 1991; 78 (Reel 53)
    Beginning at frame 01837 on Correspondence reel 14.
  - Local 471, 1991; 79 (Reel 53)
    Beginning at frame 01844 on Correspondence reel 14.
  - Local 479, 1991; 80 (Reel 53)
    Beginning at frame 01848 on Correspondence reel 14.
  - Local 483, 1991; 81 (Reel 53)
    Beginning at frame 01851 on Correspondence reel 14.
  - Local 497, 1991; 82 (Reel 53)
    Beginning at frame 01861 on Correspondence reel 14.
  - Local 498, 1991; 83 (Reel 53)
    Beginning at frame 01866 on Correspondence reel 14.
  - Local 531, 1991; 84 (Reel 53)
    Beginning at frame 01870 on Correspondence reel 14.
  - Local 533, 1991; 85 (Reel 53)
    Beginning at frame 01873 on Correspondence reel 14.
  - Local 535, 1991; 86 (Reel 53)
    Beginning at frame 01876 on Correspondence reel 14.
  - Local 541, 1991; 87 (Reel 53)
    Beginning at frame 01908 on Correspondence reel 14.
  - Local 550, 1991; 88 (Reel 53)
    Beginning at frame 01912 on Correspondence reel 14.
  - Local 590, 1991; 89 (Reel 53)
    Beginning at frame 01925 on Correspondence reel 14.
  - Local 610, 1991; 90 (Reel 53)
    Beginning at frame 01930 on Correspondence reel 14.
  - Local 611, 1991; 91 (Reel 53)
    Beginning at frame 01940 on Correspondence reel 14.
  - Local 623, 1991; 92 (Reel 53)
    Beginning at frame 01955 on Correspondence reel 14.
  - Local 628, 1991; 93 (Reel 53)
    Beginning at frame 01962 on Correspondence reel 14.
  - Local 631, 1991; 94 (Reel 53)
    Beginning at frame 01969 on Correspondence reel 14.
  - Local 634, 1991; 95 (Reel 53)
    Beginning at frame 01973 on Correspondence reel 14.
  - Local 636, 1991; 96 (Reel 53)
    Beginning at frame 01983 on Correspondence reel 14.
  - Local 662, 1991; 97 (Reel 53)
    Beginning at frame 01986 on Correspondence reel 14.
  - Local 681, 1991; 98 (Reel 53)
    Beginning at frame 01995 on Correspondence reel 14.
  - Local 688, 1991; 99 (Reel 53)
    Beginning at frame 02026 on Correspondence reel 14.
  - Local 719, 1991; 100 (Reel 53)
    Beginning at frame 02035 on Correspondence reel 14.
  - Local 727, 1991; 101 (Reel 53)
    Beginning at frame 02040 on Correspondence reel 14.
  - Local 737, 1991; 102 (Reel 53)
    Beginning at frame 02043 on Correspondence reel 14.
  - Local 767, 1991; 103 (Reel 53)
    Beginning at frame 02052 on Correspondence reel 14.
  - Local 772, 1991; 104 (Reel 53)
    Beginning at frame 02058 on Correspondence reel 14.
  - Local 775, 1991; 105 (Reel 53)
    Beginning at frame 02062 on Correspondence reel 14.
  - Local 779, 1991; 106 (Reel 53)
    Beginning at frame 02075 on Correspondence reel 14.
  - Local 791, 1991; 107 (Reel 53)
    Beginning at frame 02079 on Correspondence reel 14.
  - Local 804, 1991; 108 (Reel 53)
    Beginning at frame 02084 on Correspondence reel 14.
  - Local 814, 1991; 109 (Reel 53)
    Beginning at frame 02095 on Correspondence reel 14.
  - Local 847, 1991; 110 (Reel 53)
    Beginning at frame 02126 on Correspondence reel 14.
  - Local 863, 1991; 111 (Reel 53)
    Beginning at frame 02129 on Correspondence reel 14.
  - Local 878, 1991; 112 (Reel 53)
    Beginning at frame 02134 on Correspondence reel 14.
  - Local 879, 1991; 113 (Reel 53)
    Beginning at frame 02150 on Correspondence reel 14.
  - Local 886, 1991; 114 (Reel 53)
    Beginning at frame 02159 on Correspondence reel 14.
  - I.P.S.S.E.U. Locals., 1991; 115 (Reel 53)
    Beginning at frame 02166 on Correspondence reel 14.
- Series General Secretary-Treasurer. Local Correspondence. 1992-1993.
  - Local 1, 1992-1993; 1 (Reel 54)
    Beginning at frame 00005 on Correspondence reel 15.
  - Local 2, 1992-1993; 2 (Reel 54)
    Beginning at frame 00027 on Correspondence reel 15.
  - Local 3, 1992-1993; 3 (Reel 54)
    Beginning at frame 00098 on Correspondence reel 15.
  - Local 4, 1992-1993; 4 (Reel 54)
    Beginning at frame 00119 on Correspondence reel 15.
  - Local 5, 1992-1993; 5 (Reel 54)
    Beginning at frame 00200 on Correspondence reel 15.
  - Local 6, 1992-1993; 6 (Reel 54)
    Beginning at frame 00219 on Correspondence reel 15.
  - Local 7, 1992-1993; 7 (Reel 54)
    Beginning at frame 00380 on Correspondence reel 15.
  - Local 8, 1992-1993; 8 (Reel 54)
    Beginning at frame 00389 on Correspondence reel 15.
  - Local 9, 1992-1993; 9 (Reel 54)
    Beginning at frame 00461 on Correspondence reel 15.
  - Local 10, 1992-1993; 10 (Reel 54)
    Beginning at frame 00519 on Correspondence reel 15.
  - Local 11, 1992-1993; 11 (Reel 54)
    Beginning at frame 00537 on Correspondence reel 15.
  - Local 12, 1992-1993; 12 (Reel 54)
    Beginning at frame 00614 on Correspondence reel 15.
  - Local 14, 1992-1993; 13 (Reel 54)
    Beginning at frame 00687 on Correspondence reel 15.
  - Local 16, 1992-1993; 14 (Reel 54)
    Beginning at frame 00706 on Correspondence reel 15.
  - Local 17, 1992-1993; 15 (Reel 54)
    Beginning at frame 00736 on Correspondence reel 15.
  - Local 18, 1992-1993; 16 (Reel 54)
    Beginning at frame 00739 on Correspondence reel 15.
  - Local 19, 1992-1993; 17 (Reel 54)